easypano.com 2006-12-12

# Virtual Tour Software, Panorama Software and Photo Stitching Software Developer: Easypano

| 

Easypano Commitment To Privacy

  1. **Easypano's commitment regarding disclosure of member information**  
Easypano will not share member information with third parties without permission.  

  2. **Product activation and privacy**
  
Easypano products may require activation in order to authenticate licensed users. The Easypano Product Activation System does not collect or utilize personal information, such as your name and contact information. Product Activation is completely secure and anonymous. No personal information is ever collected or requested. During activation, the product does not scan your hard drives or collect any data other than the minimum information required to verify your license.
  3.  **Unsubscribe freely from any Easypano email**  
You can unsubscribe from any email list at any time from Easypano Newsletter.

Easypano Privacy Policy 

Information Collection and Use    
Easypano is the sole owner of the information collected on this Web site. Any information collected from our users will not be sold, shared, or rented to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. 

Easypano Member and Product Registration  
You will become a Easypano member automatically when you successfully order a product on Easypano Website. An Email with your login Email and password will be sent to you once we receive your order. However, if you order products from our distributors and resellers, you have to register as an Easypano member by registering a product with information such as Email address, your first name, last name, product serial number and license key. This data is used to provide information about the services on our site for which the user has expressed an interest. It is optional for the user to give demographic information, but encouraged, so that we can provide a more tailored experience on our site. To confirm registration, we send all new members and product registrants a welcoming e-mail. 

Online Purchases   
We use an outside company, element 5, to ship orders and process credit cards. This company does not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.  
On our order form, a user is asked to provide contact information (e.g. name and address) and payment information (e.g. credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes, to fill customer's orders and, if the customer chooses, may be used for future promotional offers. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information will be used to get in touch with the user. 

Cookies    
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in NO WAY linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates.   
Cookies provide a more tailored and convenient experience for users. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to login more than once, thereby saving time. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to further enhance the experience on our site. Rejecting a cookie will limit users to some areas of our site. 

Log Files   
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.   

Sharing   
We will ONLY share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is NOT linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.   
As mentioned above, an outside company called Element 5 processes online orders. This company does not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.  
Sometimes we partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these specific services, we will share ONLY information that is necessary for the third party to provide these specific services. These third parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.  

Links  
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

Newsletters  
If a user wishes to subscribe to our Newsletters, we only ask for the user's e-mail address.   

Surveys & Contests  
From time-to-time our site will request information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary, and, therefore, the user has the choice of whether or not to disclose such information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. 

Trial Downloads  
Many Easypano products have trial software available for downloading. During the trial download process, the user has a choice to opt-in or -out of certain options. For example, these may include the option to receive occasional Easypano product news and special offers via e-mail. 

Security   
This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, your information is protected both online and off-line. 

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is protected with the best encryption software in the industry: Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape? Navigator and Microsoft? Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to unlocked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'. To learn more about SSL, follow this link <http://www.verisign.com/site/ssl.html>

At Easypano, we also do everything in our power to protect user information off-line. All of our users' information remains confidential in our offices. Only a selected number of employees who need the information to perform a specific job (e.g. a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. These employees must also use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up to date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected. Finally, the servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment, behind locked doors.

If you have any questions about the security on our Web site, you can send an e-mail to Easypano. 

Special Offers  
Due to their request, established members will occasionally receive information about products, services, special deals, and a News Flash. Out of respect for the privacy of our users, we provide the option to discontinue these types of communications. For more details, please see the Choice/Opt-out paragraph below.   
Modifying/Updating Personal Information  
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as the postal code) or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data. This is done at the member information page. 

Choice/Opt-out  
Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials may opt-out of receiving these communications by modifing your mailing status here. 

Notification of Changes  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our home page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we would notify users by way of an e-mail. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

|
